[Music]
I'm big ass Lincoln chaffy and a change
party and I'm going to make this world
better that's what I'm talking about 2
come on man that's how you do it right
there ladies and Gentlemen even though
the laws have changed Banks like
associated in 2015 are still getting
busted for turning down black and Latino
applicants in disproportionate numbers
when on paper they're exactly as
qualified as white applicants well you
know I just say it's good now that they
have to pay the settlement and part of
the settlement is that now they have to
they have to offer loans to minority
markets and pay for things like enhanced
training and the bake Union has a new
slogan Associated now forceably
resentfully associated with
negro we can't even handle a woman
President we haven't had one yet every
other country damn near is Pakistan had
a female president come what is the
Prejudice for like a a single woman at
that age they think she's going to bring
cats into the White House
the nightly show comedy central like us
on Facebook too just don't poke me I do
not like being poked you can Candy Crush
me